

PERSONAL

Birthday : 31th October 1995

Relationship : Single
Nationality : Indonesia
Languages : Bahasa, English

SKILLS

LARAVEL PHP

JAVASCRIPT

VUE JS

REACT JS

JAVA

MYSQL

HTML 5

CSS 3

SASS

GIT NPM

CONTACT



+62 822 192 981 28



bonabriansiagian@gmail.com



Kp Tugumulya RT 04 RW 01 Kab. Bandung, Jawa Barat



https://github.com/bonabrian



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bonabrian/

BONA BRIAN SIAGIAN

Web Developer

PROFILE

I'M Bona Brian Siagian. I'm a Software Engineer working on Web Applications. Design and developed applications from use cases and functional requirements. Creative web developer dedicated to developing and optimizing interactive, user-friendly, and feature-rich websites. Leverage analytical skills and strong attention to detail in order to deliver efficient web application, provide technical knowledge and expertise, build new websites from start to finish on schedule.

I'm enthuasiastic, responsible and hard working IT person. Being worked for different projects helped me to adopt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I've been developing professionally for over 2 years but tinkering since a kid. I started in tech with freelance services during college.

Education

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

Indonesian Computer University (UNIKOM) Bachelor Degree GPA 3.11 2013 - 2018

Experience

Web Developer

June 2018 - Now

PT. Varnion Technology Semesta (Jakarta) | www.varnion.com Work as fullstack engineer to build internal projects from scratch and several external projects.

Portfolio

Wikas February 2020 - Now

www.wikas.id

A news portal website.

Build a REST API, and fulstack website.

Brivia September 2019 - Now

Personal Project

A big Indonesian marketplace.

Build Indonesian marketplace, implement payment gateway.

As fullstack web developer.

Nazar

October 2019 - February 2020

Build a multivendor ecommerce app. As a android developer.

More portfolio on https://bonabrian.github.io/